<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GenCloth</title>
    <link>https://gencloth.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GenCloth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 19:27:17 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gencloth.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop</title>
      <link>https://gencloth.com/log/2018/10/01/workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 19:27:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gencloth.com/log/2018/10/01/workshop/</guid>
      <description>You are invited to a 3 day workshop on digital technologies for the future of fashion design!
Advanced digital technologies allow us to rethink the process of traditional fashion design and pattern drafting. Are you interested in envisioning how we will design and consume fashion in 2030?
We’d like designers to spend some time with our digital tools, create body scans and design in 3D, discussing digital design processes and the future of fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World.</title>
      <link>https://gencloth.com/log/2018/06/12/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gencloth.com/log/2018/06/12/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>Hello World, we are GenCloth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gencloth.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gencloth.com/about/</guid>
      <description>“There is no going back. Study the past to know why, not what, and from the why, dream and do.  There is no shortcut to creation.” ― Elizabeth Ann Coleman, The Genius of Charles James 

GenCloth aims to empower local fashion designers with 3D software toolkits for rapid client customization in order to grow local economies and the next generation of fashion designers. The toolkit includes software plugin tools and databases to aid in designing customized pieces for clientele, speed up production timelines within local micro factories, and aid in the production of durable and sustainable designs that add value into fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gencloth.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gencloth.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Please feel free to contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://gencloth.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gencloth.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Development Goals</title>
      <link>https://gencloth.com/sdgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gencloth.com/sdgs/</guid>
      <description>GenCloth focuses on contributing to the achievement of six of the United Nations’s Sustainable Development Goals for 2030.



SDG 5 Gender Equality - by enhancing the use of enabling technology, in particular information and communications technology, to promote the empowerment of women. “At an avg. of 68%, women represent the largest group within the garment workforce&amp;hellip;.the empowerment of women is depicted as a prerequisite to the eradication of poverty and sustainable growth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>